{"test_questions": [[{"question": "An intrusion detection system does not perform which of the following?", "opta": "Tries to identify attempts to hack into a computer system.", "optb": "May monitor packets passing over the network.", "optc": "May transmit message packets to the correct destination.", "optd": "Set up deception systems that attempt to trap hackers.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Features of XML include which of the following?", "opta": "The tags are used to describe the appearance of the content.", "optb": "Addresses the structuring and manipulation of the data involved.", "optc": "Governs the display of information in a Web browser.", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is Hypertext Transfer Protocol (HTTP)?", "opta": "The protocol to copy files between computers", "optb": "The transfer protocol to transfer Web pages to a browser", "optc": "The database access protocol for SQL statements", "optd": "The hardware/software protocol that limits access to company data", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is true concerning Web services standards?", "opta": "Led by only one group.", "optb": "Helped by cooperation between companies.", "optc": "Not necessary at this time.", "optd": "Important so that the web can flourish.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Common Gateway Interface (CGI) is which of the following?", "opta": "An interface that accepts and returns data that may be written in SQL.", "optb": "An interface that accepts and returns data that may be written in any language that produces an executable file.", "optc": "A small program that executes within another application and is stored on the server.", "optd": "A small program that executes within another application and is stored on the client.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A server-side extension is needed to do what?", "opta": "Allow a request from a client to access the database.", "optb": "Allow a request from a client to access a HTML-formatted page.", "optc": "Allow a request from a client to access Web pages.", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is true about ColdFusion Markup Language (CFML)?", "opta": "It is stored in .asp files.", "optb": "It is executed on the client.", "optc": "It does not use tags.", "optd": "It allows for coding of custom tags in an HTML file.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "XML is which of the following?", "opta": "A scripting language that states the rules for tagging elements.", "optb": "A programming language that states the rules for tagging elements.", "optc": "A programming language that allows the creation of customized tags.", "optd": "A scripting language that allows the creation of customized tags.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "An intranet provides which of the following?", "opta": "Connectivity to all customers", "optb": "Connectivity to selected customers", "optc": "Connectivity to no customers", "optd": "Connectivity to all of the above", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Client-side extensions:", "opta": "add functionality to the server.", "optb": "add functionality to the browser.", "optc": "add functionality to the firewall.", "optd": "add functionality to the network.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is true about Microsoft Active Server Pages (ASP)?", "opta": "It is stored in .cfm files.", "optb": "It is executed on the client.", "optc": "It does not use tags.", "optd": "It allows for coding of custom tags in an HTML file.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Websites without a database attached to them have which of the following characteristics?", "opta": "The ability to generate data via SQL.", "optb": "The inability to use a browser to display Web pages.", "optc": "Static information using HTML or JavaScript.", "optd": "The need to use TCP/IP as the network protocol.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Web servers should be configured in which of the following ways?", "opta": "unauthorized access is restricted.", "optb": "unauthorized access is unrestricted.", "optc": "unauthorized access is impossible.", "optd": "unauthorized access is possible.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A proxy server is used for which of the following?", "opta": "To provide security against unauthorized users", "optb": "To process client requests for Web pages", "optc": "To process client requests for database access", "optd": "To provide TCP/IP", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is true concerning the standard network protocol for connecting a client to a Web or database server via the Internet?", "opta": "Both TCP and IP are needed.", "optb": "TCP is needed but IP is not needed.", "optc": "TCP is not needed but IP is needed.", "optd": "Neither TCP and IP are needed.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}